sportsauthority.com 2015-09-05

# Help - SportsAuthority.com

|  Safety, Security and Privacy  
---  
   »| [Secure Shopping Guarantee](http://www.sportsauthority.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?display=safety&subdisplay=secure)  
   »| [Terms & Conditions](http://www.sportsauthority.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?display=safety&subdisplay=terms)  
   »| [Service Plan](http://www.sportsauthority.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?display=safety&subdisplay=warranty)  
   »| [Privacy Policy](http://www.sportsauthority.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?display=safety&subdisplay=privacy)  
   »| [MasterCard SecureCode](http://www.sportsauthority.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?display=safety&subdisplay=mastercard&topic=securecode)  
   »| [Verified by Visa](http://www.sportsauthority.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?display=safety&subdisplay=vbv&topic=vbv)  
---  
 **Sports Authority Privacy Policy |En Espanol**  
  
 _Updated November 6, 2013_

TSA Stores, Inc. ("SA," "Us," "We," and "Our") operates retail brick-and-mortar stores and websites ("Websites") and has created this Privacy Policy to inform you of Our collection, use and sharing practices for information we collect from you.

Because We want to demonstrate Our commitment to your privacy, We want to notify you of:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours we collect;
  2. Who is collecting the information;
  3. How the information is used;
  4. With whom the information may be shared;
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Our control; and
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information We collect.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact our Customer Service Department by email at [customerservice@thesportsauthority.com](mailto://customerservice@thesportsauthority.com), by completing the Customer Feedback Form in the Helpdesk section or by phone at 1.888.801.9164 or write us at: Sports Authority 15 S Babcock Street Melbourne, FL 32901

Visiting www.sportsauthority.com

By visiting our Website or providing us with information in our stores or online, you signify your consent to the collection, use and sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy. By providing your information to Us, you signify your consent to the information collection, use and sharing practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Types of Information Collected

We collect personal and non-personal information that you provide to Us when using our Websites or that you give to us in our stores or to Our Customer Service Department when communicating with Us offline or via e-mail.

Personal information that you provide to Us, such as your full name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number and credit card expiration date, is collected, stored and used only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed at the time We request such information from you. For example, when you open an account or place an order, We collect and store some or all of the personal information that you provide. This personal information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process and ship orders, to send order and shipping confirmations and to provide customer service. This personal information also may be used to contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications from Us.

We also collect non-personal information about users of Our Websites. The non-personal information we collect on our Websites is information that by itself cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information and other anonymous statistical data relating to the use of this Website. For example, we collect and store certain non-personal information automatically whenever you interact with this Website, including your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name. We also collect non-personal information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve our Websites and to provide Our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience.

Your IP address, browser and reference site domain name are logged every time you visit Our Websites. This data is used strictly for the analysis of load information and maximizing the efficiency of Our servers. Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not share this data with anyone in any way.

Subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, any communication or material you give to Us or transmit or post to this Website by email or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, or suggestions (other than personally identifiable information which will be treated in accordance with this privacy policy), is and will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and anything you give or transmit or post may be used by Us and Our affiliates for any purpose, including without limitation, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast, and posting. We are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication or material that you give to us or send to our Websites for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products using such information.

Cookies, Web Beacons and Targeted Advertising

Also, like many web sites, We use "cookies" on our Websites which are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. These cookies help Us identify Our account holders and optimize their shopping experience. They do not include any data that will identify you personally. They will, however, allow you to use some specialized features of the Websites. Cookies also allow Us to hold selections in your shopping cart when you leave Our Websites without checking out. Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but allow you to disable them if you wish.

Most browsers provide you with the option to set your browser to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or to not receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalized services cannot then be provided to you and accordingly you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the features on Our Websites.

We may use third-party advertising companies to provide Us with data collection and reporting services regarding Our guests' activities in our stores and on Our Websites, tracking and measuring performance of Our marketing efforts and your response to Our marketing efforts, and the delivery of relevant marketing messages. On Our Websites, these companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness and may receive information about your browsing and buying activity on Our Websites. Web beacons enable Us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits one of Our Websites and to learn which banner ads bring users to Our Websites. In addition, We and Our third party service providers may use cookies to manage and track the performance of Our advertisements displayed on other websites across the Internet.

Targeted advertising (also known as online behavioral advertising) uses information collected on an individual's web browsing behavior, such as the pages they have visited or the searches they have made. This information is then used to select which of Our advertisements should be displayed to a particular individual on websites other than our Websites. The information collected is only linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address or credit card number. The information used for targeted advertising either comes from Us or through third party website publishers. If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising that occurs on Our third party advertising publishers, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. Please note that this will opt you out of targeted ads from Us and any other participating advertisers. If you opt out, you will continue to receive online advertising from Us; however, these ads may not be as relevant to you.

External Links/Framed Pages

Our Website store locator functionality links to a third party web site. Any data provided through this functionality is not governed by this Privacy Policy. The privacy policy of the third party web site governs the information collection and dissemination practices occurring on such web site.

If you have accessed one of our Websites through a link from certain of Our advertising and marketing partners, Our Websites may include a frame of the applicable advertising and marketing partner. The information you provide to Us through these framed web pages is collected by Us and its use is governed by this Privacy Policy.

Ordering from Our Websites

When you order from one of Our Websites, We need your name, email address, shipping address, phone number and credit card number/expiration date. We use this data to process your order, ship it and send you order and shipping confirmations via email. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, We will not sell, rent, or disclose this data to any third party without your consent. (However, We will cooperate fully should a situation arise where We are required by law or requested by a law enforcement agency to provide information about a customer.)

From time to time, We use the purchases you make to customize Our product recommendations. We also track customer traffic patterns and site usage. Traffic and usage data is used only to improve Our Websites' designs and provide Our customers with a fulfilling shopping experience.

Opening an Account

We require your name, billing address, shipping address, email address and telephone number to open an account for you on our Websites. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, this account data is never shared with anyone in any way without your consent. (However, We will cooperate fully should a situation arise where We are required by law or requested by a law enforcement agency to provide information about a customer.)

Corrections/Updates to your Account

You can correct you account data on our Websites by clicking on "My Account". If you have any questions or concerns about correcting or updating your Account, please contact Our Customer Service Department.

Receiving Promotions/Opt-Out

From time to time, We will contact you about sales, special offers and new site features if you agreed to be included in Our email lists when you completed a purchase transaction with Us or otherwise provided us with your information. To customize the information you want to receive from Us on our Websites, simply sign on and select the specific information you wish to receive. To cancel Our free emails, follow the directions in the email communication you received from us. You can also send an email by completing the Customer Feedback Form in the Helpdesk section or call Us toll-free at 1-888-801-9164 and inform Us that you want to unsubscribe to Our email list or, write us at: Sports Authority 15 S Babcock Street Melbourne, FL 32901

Customer Service

In addition to being able to call Our customer service department at 1-888-801-9164, you may also email Us by completing the Customer Feedback Form in the Helpdesk section of our Websites. When you email Us, your emails are stored within Our system so that We may refer to previous emails from you as needed so that We may properly address your questions and concerns. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, the information you provide to Our customer service department is not shared with anyone without your consent.

Entering Contests/Sweepstakes

Whenever We run a contest or sweepstakes, it will be accompanied with the rules of the contest/sweepstakes. We will also describe how the information gathered from you for entry into the contest/sweepstakes will be used. Additionally, we will post if this information will be shared with anyone in addition to those persons and entities provided for in this Privacy Policy, such as a third party sponsoring or managing the contest/sweepstakes.

E-mail to a Friend

Users of our Websites have the opportunity to e-mail product pages to their friends. In order to accomplish this, you must provide to Us each such friend's name and e-mail address. We only use your friend's information to send them the product pages you request that they receive.

Online Gift Certificates and Gift Cards

If you send an online gift certificate or gift card to a third party, you must provide Us with the recipient's name and e-mail address. We only use this information to deliver such gift certificate or gift card.

Customer Feedback Form

You can use this form to give Us any input which we will use to improve Our site. The only required data is your name and email address. The remainder of the data is optional. We only use this data to make improvements on Our Websites. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, this data is not shared with anyone in any way.

Our Third Party Relationships

We have established several relationships with third parties vendors to best serve Our customers and to operate our Websites.

  *  _Third Party Service Providers:_ We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on Our behalf in connection with the operation of Our Websites. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, hosting and operating the Websites and providing customer service. These third parties have access to your information collected through Our Websites as needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  *  _Affiliates:_ From time to time, We may establish one or more affiliate programs. An affiliate program allows other web sites to earn money by linking customers to Our Websites from their sites. These affiliates can only access data about the number of transactions and their resulting earnings. They cannot access Our customers' personal data. If you choose to apply to any of Our affiliate programs, We use the data you give Us strictly for conducting business with you. We may enter into certain agreements with certain third parties for the purpose of helping to administer affiliate programs. Such third parties may have access to certain of your information if you are an affiliate of the Website, but is restricted to only use such information in connection with its administration of the affiliate programs.
  *  _Order Fulfillment and Customer Service:_ GSI and certain vendors of ours provide customer order fulfillment and shipping services and customer service on Our behalf. These vendors have access only to information needed to accurately fulfill and ship orders that are processed through such vendors and to provide customer services. These vendors have agreed to not use any personally identifiable information of customers for any other purpose.
  *  _Credit Card Processing:_ We use a third party to process credit card orders. We supply them with data for credit card authorization and fraud detection only and they are restricted from using the data for any other purposes.
  *  _Website Evaluation, Marketing and Promotions:_ From time to time, We may engage other third parties to assist in providing Website evaluation services, marketing, order processing, fulfillment and shipping services, as well as customer service. In addition, We or GSI may engage third parties to provide services such as fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product customization, data analysis and data cleansing. These third parties will only have access to information to the extent necessary and will be required to not use any personal information for any purpose other than providing such services. Also, you permit Us to share your personal information in response to a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We may transfer your personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. Additionally, We may share non-personal, non-individual statistical information with Our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties for research purposes. That is, We will not tell Our marketing partners that you purchased a specific product, but we may tell them how many customers purchased that product.

Security Policy

We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to protect your personal information. The only time you are required to sign on our Websites is when you are making a purchase. On the checkout page, you will be asked to access your existing account or create a new one. Existing account holders are prompted for their user ID (your email address) and password. This password is for your protection. If you don't have your password, there is a link that reads "Forgot your password?" Click on this for instructions on how to get your password.

Changes to Privacy Policy

If We are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, We will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not We use your information in this different manner. In addition, if We make any material changes in Our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in Our database, We will post a prominent notice on our Websites notifying users of the change. In some cases where We post the notice, We will also email users who have opted to receive communications from Us, notifying them of the changes in Our privacy practices.

Questions about Our Policies

If you have any questions regarding your privacy or any of Our policies, please contact Our Customer Service Department by completing the Customer Feedback Form in the Helpdesk section or call Us toll-free at 1-800-360-8721.

Your California Privacy Rights

Under California law, you have the right to request and receive information from retailers concerning any third parties who have received personal information about you from such retailers for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Any such requests for information from Us can be made by contacting Our Customer Service Department by completing the Customer Feedback Form in the Helpdesk section or by calling Us toll-free at 1-800-360-8721.  
  
 **Sports Authority política de privacidad |**  
  
 _Actualizada el 1ro. de abril de 2011_

Nuestra política de privacidad

TSA Stores, Inc. (“SA”, “Nosotros”, “Nos” y “Nuestro”) opera tiendas tradicionales físicas y páginas de internet (“Websites”) y ha creado esta política de privacidad para informarle a usted sobre Nuestras prácticas de divulgación, recopilación y compartir de información que recopilamos de usted.

Porque Nosotros queremos demostrarle Nuestro compromiso con su privacidad, queremos notificarle lo siguiente:

1.Cuál información identificable personalmente como suya recopilamos;  
2.Quién recopila esta información;  
3.Cómo se utiliza esta información;  
4.Con quién se comparte esta información;  
5.Qué opciones tiene usted disponibles en relación a la recopilación, uso y distribución de la información;  
6.Los tipos de procedimientos de seguridad que están activos para proteger en contra de la pérdida, el mal uso o la alteración de información bajo nuestro control; y  
7.Cómo usted puede corregir cualquier imprecisión en la información que Nosotros recopilamos.

Si usted tiene preguntas o cualquier inquietud referente a la información brindada aquí, debe contactar nuestro Departamento de Servicio al Cliente, por correo electrónico (email) a la siguiente dirección: [customerservice@thesportsauthority.com](mailto:customerservice@thesportsauthority.com); puede también completar el formulario “Customer Feedback Form” en la Sección de “Helpdesk”; o por teléfono, libre de cargos, al número 1.888.801.9164.

Al usar este Website o al proveernos información en nuestras tiendas o a través del Internet usted consigna su consentimiento a la recopilación, uso y prácticas de divulgación descritas en esta Política de Privacidad. Al proveernos su información, usted consigna su consentimiento para la recopilación, uso y prácticas de divulgación de esta información según se describen en esta Política de Privacidad. 

Recogemos información personal y no personal que usted Nos provee cuando utiliza Nuestros Websites, en nuestras tiendas o cuando se comunica con nuestro Departamento de Servicio al Cliente por medios no electrónicos o mediante correo electrónico.

Información personal que usted Nos provea como su nombre completo, dirección residencial, dirección de correo electrónico, número telefónico, número de tarjeta de crédito y la fecha de expiración de su tarjeta de crédito, se recoge, se guarda y se usa sólo para los propósitos descritos en esta Política de Privacidad, o de cualquier otra manera que se haga saber al momento de nosotros solicitarle dicha información. Por ejemplo, cuando usted abre una cuenta o coloca una orden, Nosotros recogemos y guardamos toda o alguna porción de la información personal que usted nos provee. Esta información personal se usa para proveer los productos y servicios que usted haya ordenado o requerido, para procesar y enviar sus órdenes, para enviarle confirmaciones de órdenes y de envío, y para proveerle servicio al cliente. Esta información personal también puede ser utilizada para ponernos en contacto con usted sobre ventas especiales, ofertas especiales, y nuevas características de este Website, a menos que usted haya optado por no recibir comunicaciones de promoción de Nosotros.

Nosotros también recogemos información no personal sobre los usuarios de Nuestros Websites. La información no personal que recogemos en Nuestros Websites es información que de por sí misma no puede ser usada para identificarlo o contactarlo. Se trata de información demográfica y otros datos estadísticos anónimos relacionados con el uso de este Website. Por ejemplo, recogemos y guardamos cierta información no personal automáticamente cada vez que usted interactúa con este Website, incluyendo su dirección IP, información sobre su navegador “browser”, nombre del dominio del lugar de referencia y patrones de tráfico del consumidor y del uso de este Website. Esta información se usa para analizar y mejorar Nuestros Websites y proveerle a nuestros clientes con una experiencia gratificante de compra.

Su dirección IP, de navegador “browser” y nombre del dominio del lugar de referencia, se registran cada vez que usted visita Nuestros Websites . Esta información se usa estrictamente para el análisis del peso de la información y para maximizar la eficiencia de nuestros servidores. Excepto según se provee en esta política de privacidad, Nosotros no compartiremos esta información con nadie de ninguna manera.

Sujeto a los términos y condiciones de esta Política de Privacidad, cualquier comunicación o material que usted nos brinde o transmita o publique en este Website por correo electrónico o de cualquier otra forma, incluyendo cualesquieras datos, preguntas, comentarios, o sugerencias (salvo información personal identificable, la cual será tratada de acuerdo con esta Política de Privacidad), es y será tratada como no confidencial y no propietaria y cualquier cosa que usted nos brinde, transmita, publique o postee podrá ser usada por Nosotros y por Nuestros afiliados para cualquier propósito, incluyendo, sin limitaciones, reproducción, divulgación, transmisión, publicación, transmisión en medios masivos y posteo. Estamos en libertad de usar cualquier idea, concepto, destrezas, o técnicas contenidas en cualquier comunicación o material que usted nos brinde o envíe a Nuestros Websites para cualquier propósito, que incluye, pero no se limita a, desarrollar, manufacturar y mercadear productos usando esta información.

También, como muchas páginas de internet, usamos “cookies”en Nuestros Websites, que son archivos que su navegador “browser” guarda en el disco duro de su computadora. Estos “cookies” Nos ayudan a identificar Nuestros tenedores de cuentas y optimizar su experiencia de compra. No incluyen información que lo identifique a usted personalmente. Sin embargo, permitirán que usted pueda usar algunos atributos especializados de los Websites. Los “cookies” también Nos permiten retener sus selecciones en su carro de compras aún cuando usted abandone Nuestros Websites antes de finalizar la compra. Casi todos los navegadores “browsers” aceptan “cookies” automáticamente, pero le permiten a usted desactivarlos si usted lo prefiere.

La mayoría de los navegadores “browsers” le proveen a usted con la opción de configurarlos para aceptar todos los “cookies”, para que usted sea notificado cuando algún “cookie” le es emitido, o para no aceptar ningún “cookie” en ningún momento. Esta última opción, por supuesto, significa que ciertos servicios personalizados del Website no estarán disponibles para usted y que de esta manera usted no podrá hacer uso máximo de todas las ventajas y atributos que ofrecen Nuestros Websites.

Podemos usar compañías publicitarias externas a Nosotros para proveernos servicios de recopilación de información y de reportaje relacionados con las actividades de nuestros visitantes en nuestras tiendas y enNuestros Websites, rastreando y midiendo el desempeño de Nuestros esfuerzos de mercadeo y sus respuestas a esos esfuerzos Nuestros de mercadeo, y el envío a usted de mensajes pertinentes sobre esos esfuerzos de mercadeo. En Nuestros Websites, estas compañías pueden emplear “cookies” y “action tags” (también conocidos como “single pixel gifs” o “web beacons”) para medir la efectividad de la publicidad y pueden recibir información sobre su actividad de navegación y de compra en Nuestros Websites. Los “web beacons” nos permiten reconocer los “cookies” de un “browser” cuando un “browser” navega Nuestros Websites y aprender qué anuncios pueden atraer usuarios a Nuestros Websites. En adición, Nosotros y Nuestros proveedores de servicios externos a Nosotros pueden usar estos “cookies” para manejar y rastrear el desempeño de Nuestra publicidad desplegada en otros “websites” a través de la internet.

La publicidad enfocada (también conocida como publicidad situacional en línea) usa esta información recogida en la conducta de un individuo usando su navegador “browser”, tal como las páginas que visita o las búsquedas que hace. Esta información entonces se usa para seleccionar cuál de Nuestros anuncios deben ser desplegados para un individuo particular en lugares del internet diferentes a Nuestros Websites. La información recogida sólo se vincula a un identificador de “cookie” anónimo (código alfa numérico); no incluye ninguna información que pueda vincularlo a usted de manera personal, como su nombre, dirección o número de tarjeta de crédito. La información usada para la publicidad enfocada o viene de Nosotros o a través de publicistas de la internet externos a Nosotros. Si usted prefiere desactivar este tipo de publicidad que promueven nuestros publicistas de la internet externos a Nosotros, contratados por Nosotros, por favor, visite: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt__out.asp>. Por favor, tome nota de que de esta manera se desactiva la publicidad enfocada Nuestra y de otros anunciantes participantes. De todas maneras usted continuará recibiendo publicidad en línea de parte Nuestra; sin embargo, estos anuncios pueden resultar no ser de su interés particular.

La funcionalidad de nuestro localizador de tienda en Nuestros Websites se enlaza con un “web site” externo de terceros. Cualquier información que se suministre a través de esta funcionalidad no queda gobernada por esta Política de Privacidad. La Política de Privacidad de los terceros gobernará la información que se recoge en su “web site” y sus prácticas de divulgación.

Si usted hubiera accedido a cualquiera de Nuestros Websites a través de un enlace con alguno de Nuestros anunciantes o socios de mercadeo, Nuestros Websites puede incluir un marco con la publicidad aplicable y Nuestro socio de mercadeo. La información que se Nos provea a través de estas páginas enmarcadas es recopilada por Nosotros y su uso está gobernado por esta Política de Privacidad.

Cuando usted hace órdenes en cualquiera de Nuestros Websites, necesitamos su nombre, dirección de correo electrónico, dirección de envío, número telefónico y número de tarjeta de crédito con su fecha de expiración. Usamos estos datos para procesar sus órdenes, embarcarlas y enviarle a usted la confirmación de orden y de embarque por correo electrónico. A excepción de como se describe en esta Política de Privacidad, Nosotros no venderemos, alquilaremos, o divulgaremos esta información a terceros sin su consentimiento. (Sin embargo, de surgir una situación que lo requiera legalmente, o haya un pedido de alguna agencia de ley, se le proveerá información sobre el cliente y brindaremos toda nuestra cooperación.)

De tiempo en tiempo usaremos las compras que usted efectúe para ajustar a sus intereses Nuestras recomendaciones de productos. Nosotros también rastrearemos información sobre patrones de tráfico del cliente y su navegación por Nuestros Websites. Datos sobre el tráfico y el uso de Nuestros Websites se utilizan únicamente para mejorar el diseño de Nuestros Websites y proveer a Nuestros clientes con una experiencia de compra gratificante.

Se requerirá su nombre, dirección de facturación, dirección de envío, dirección de correo electrónico, y número telefónico para abrirle una cuenta en Nuestros Websites. Excepto según se provee en esta Política de Privacidad, estos datos de su cuenta nunca se comparten con nadie de ninguna manera sin su consentimiento. (Sin embargo, de surgir una situación que lo requiera legalmente, o haya un pedido de alguna agencia de ley, se le proveerá información sobre el cliente y brindaremos toda nuestra cooperación.)

Usted puede corregir la información de su cuenta en Nuestros Websites haciendo clic en el enlace titulado “My Account”. Si usted tiene alguna pregunta o alguna inquietud en relación a la actualización de su propia cuenta, por favor, contacte a Nuestro Departamento de Servicio al Cliente.

De tiempo en tiempo, Nos comunicaremos con usted en torno a ventas, ofertas especiales y nuevas opciones del Website, si usted accedió a ser incluido en Nuestra lista de correos electrónicos al completar una transacción de compra con Nosotros o de alguna otra forma nos ha provisto su información. Para personalizar a sus intereses particulares la información que usted quiere recibir de Nosotros en Nuestros Websites, acceda a su cuenta y seleccione la información específica que usted desea recibir. Para cancelar nuestros correos electrónicos gratis, siga las instrucciones contenidas en el correo electrónico que usted recibió de Nuestra parte.También puede enviarnos un correo completando el formulario “Customer Feedback Form” en la Sección de “Helpdesk”, o puede llamarnos libre de cargos al 1-888-801-9164, e indicarnos que usted quiere terminar su subscripción de Nuestras listas de correos electrónicos.

Además de poder llamar libre de cargos a Nuestro Departamento de Servicio al Cliente al 1-888-801-9164, también Nos puede enviar un correo electrónico completando el formulario “Customer Feedback Form” en la Sección de “Helpdesk” de Nuestros Websites. Cuando usted Nos envía un correo electrónico, sus correos se archivan dentro de Nuestro sistema para poder referirnos a correos electrónicos previos suyos según sea necesario, de manera que Nosotros podamos abordar y clarificar sus preguntas e inquietudes adecuadamente. Excepto como se describe en esta Política de Privacidad, la información que usted le provee a Nuestro Departamento de Servicio al Cliente no se comparte con nadie sin su consentimiento.

En cualquier momento que Nosotros efectuemos un concurso o rifa, acompañaremos las reglas del concurso/rifa. Nosotros también describiremos cómo usaremos la información recogida en su proceso de participación en el concurso/rifa. Adicionalmente, postearemos si esta información será compartida con cualquiera en adición a aquellas personas y entidades descritas en esta Política de Privacidad, como terceros, que pudieran auspiciar o manejar el concurso/rifa. 

Usuarios de Nuestros Websites tienen la oportunidad de enviarle páginas de productos a sus amigos por correo electrónico. Para efectuar esta acción, usted debe proveernos con los nombres y direcciones de correo electrónico de cada uno de sus amigos que usted quiera que reciban la(a) página(s). Sólo usamos la información de sus amigos para enviarles las páginas de productos que usted Nos hubiera solicitado que se les facilitaran.

Si usted envía un certificado de regalo en línea o una tarjeta de regalo a un tercero, usted deberá proveernos con el nombre y la dirección de correo electrónico de quien debe recibirlo. Nosotros usaremos esta información solamente para entregar dicho certificado de regalo o la tarjeta de regalo.

Usted puede usar este formulario para brindarnos cualquier insumo que podamos usar para mejorar Nuestro Website. La única información requerida es su nombre y dirección de correo electrónico. Es opcional brindarnos el resto de la información. Usamos estos datos solamente para hacer mejoras a Nuestros Websites. Excepto como se provee en esta Política de Privacidad, esta información no se comparte con nadie de ninguna manera.

Hemos establecido varias relaciones con terceros proveedores de servicios y/o afiliados para servir mejor a Nuestros clientes y para operar Nuestros Websites.

  *  _Terceros proveedores de servicios:_ Empleamos otras compañías e individuos para efectuar funciones en favor Nuestro en relación con la operación de Nuestros Websites. Ejemplos incluyen el satisfacer órdenes, entregar paquetes, enviar correos electrónicos y correos postales, remover información repetitiva de nuestras listas de clientes, analizar datos, proveer asistencia de mercadeo, proveer resultados de búsquedas y enlaces (incluyendo publicaciones pagadas y otros enlaces), procesar pagos con tarjetas de crédito, alojar y operar Nuestros Websites y proveer servicios al cliente. Estos terceros proveedores tienen acceso a información suya recogida en Nuestros Websites según la necesiten para efectuar sus funciones, pero no pueden utilizarla para ningún otro propósito.
  *  _Afiliados:_ De tiempo en tiempo podemos establecer uno o más programas de afiliados. Un programa de afiliados permite que otros dueños de “web sites” puedan ganar dinero conectando sus clientes a Nuestros Websites. Estos afiliados pueden acceder solamente a información sobre el número de transacciones y sus recaudos. No pueden acceder información personal sobre Nuestros clientes. Si usted escoge solicitar participar en cualquiera de Nuestros programas de afiliados, Nosotros usamos la información que usted Nos brinde estrictamente para conducir Nuestros negocios con usted. Podemos llegar a ciertos acuerdos con ciertos terceros con el fin de ayudar a administrar los programas de afiliados. Estos terceros pueden tener acceso a parte de su información si usted es un afiliado de Nuestro Website, pero están impedidos a usar esta información que no sea en conexión con la administración de los programas de afiliados.
  *  _Satisfacción de órdenes y Servicio al Cliente:_ GSI y algunos de nuestros proveedores nos brindan servicios de satisfacción de órdenes de clientes, servicios de envío y servicios al cliente en favor Nuestro. Estos proveedores tienen acceso solamente a la información que necesitan para satisfacer con exactitud órdenes que procedan a través de estos proveedores, y enviarlas, además de proveer servicios al cliente. Estos proveedores tienen acuerdos con Nosotros de no usar ninguna información de Nuestros clientes que pueda ser identificada individual o personalmente para ningún otro fin.
  *  _Procesamiento de tarjetas de crédito:_ Usamos terceros proveedores para procesar órdenes con tarjetas de crédito. Solamente les suministramos datos sobre autorización de tarjetas de crédito y detección de fraudes y ellos están impedidos a usar esos datos con propósitos que no sean los acordados.
  *  _Evaluación de Nuestro Website, mercadeo y promociones:_ De tiempo en tiempo podemos contratar terceros proveedores para que Nos suministren servicios de evaluación de Nuestro Website, mercadeo, procesamiento de órdenes, servicios de satisfacción de órdenes y envío, así como de servicio al cliente. En adición Nosotros o GSI podemos contratar terceros proveedores para que Nos suministren servicios como protección de fraude, y reducción de riesgo de crédito, adecuación de productos, y análisis y limpieza de datos. Estos terceros tendrán acceso a información exclusivamente según sea necesario y estarán requeridos a no usar ninguna información personal para ningún otro propósito que no sea proveer estos servicios. De igual manera, usted Nos permitirá compartir su información personal en respuesta a una orden del tribunal, emplazamientos, investigaciones gubernamentales, o de alguna otra forma requerida por ley. Podemos transferir su información personal en el evento de una venta corporativa, consolidación, adquisición, disolución, o cualquier evento similar. Adicionalmente, Nosotros podremos compartir información estadística no personal, no individual, con Nuestros socios de mercadeo, anunciantes o terceros proveedores de investigación. Es decir, no le informaremos a Nuestros socios de mercadeo que usted hizo la compra de ningún producto en específico, pero podremos informarles cuántos clientes compraron ese producto.

Política de Seguridad

Usamos tecnología de cifrar datos “Secure Socket Layer” (SSL) para proteger su información personal. La única ocasión en que se requiere que usted se inscriba a Nuestros Websites es cuando usted va a efectuar una compra. En la página donde se completa la compra, a usted se le pedirá que acceda a su cuenta existente, o que proceda a crear una cuenta nueva. A los clientes con cuentas existentes, se les insta a entrar su nombre de usuario (su dirección de correo electrónico) y su contraseña. Esta contraseña es para su protección. Si usted no recuerda su contraseña, hay un enlace que lee “Forgot your password?”. Haga clic aquí para recibir instrucciones sobre cómo recuperar su contraseña.

Si fuéramos a usar su información identificable personalmente en alguna manera diferente a la que se informó al momento de ser recogida, Nosotros se lo notificaremos por correo electrónico. Usted tendrá la opción de indicarnos si acepta o no que usemos su información en esta manera diferente. Adicionalmente, si decidimos efectuar cualquier cambio material en Nuestras prácticas de privacidad que no afecten la información de los usuarios que ya hubiera sido recogida y almacenada en nuestras bases de datos, postearemos una notificación prominente en Nuestros Websites, notificando a los usuarios sobre este cambio. En algunos casos cuando se publique esta notificación, también le notificaremos por correo electrónico a los usuarios que hayan optado por recibir comunicaciones de parte Nuestra, notificándoles de los cambios en Nuestras prácticas de privacidad.

Si usted tiene cualquier pregunta relacionada con su privacidad o con cualquiera de nuestras políticas, por favor contacte a Nuestro Departamento de Servicio al Cliente completando el formulario “Customer Feedback Form” en la Sección “Helpdesk”, o llámenos sin cargos al 1-800-360-8721.

Bajo la ley de California, usted tiene el derecho de requerir y recibir información de los detallistas en relación a terceros que hayan recibido información personal suya, de parte de esos detallistas, para programas de mercadeo de esos terceros. Cualquier pedido de información Nuestra se puede efectuar contactando Nuestro servicio de Departamento al Cliente y completando el formulario “Customer Feedback Form” en la Sección de “Helpdesk”, o llamándonos libre de cargos al 1-800-360-8721.
